(Howard:)and that didn't
even crack my top ten.
(Leonard:)I guess the difference is,
I have some self-respect.
(Howard:)Not that I've ever seen.
(Leonard:)It's relatively new.
(Leonard:)I just know that
(Leonard:)I'm not gonna spend time
with someone I don't like
(Leonard:)simply to have a girlfriend.
(Leonard:)I'm okay on my own.
(Joy:)Good news-- I made
lots of room for dessert.
(Leonard:)Look, uh, Joy, it was nice
to meet you, but...
(Joy:)Yeah, you, too.
Hey, you got anything for next weekend?
(Joy:)I need a date for
my cousin's wedding.
(Leonard:)You're asking me out?
(Stuart:)Yeah.
(Joy:)And it's an open bar,
(Joy:)so I'll probably
be giving it away.
(Leonard:)I look forward to it.
MRS. FOWLER
It's nice to meet you, too, Sheldon.
(Mrs Fowler(on webcam):)I honestly didn't believe Amy
(Mrs Fowler(on webcam):)when she told me
she had a boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)I assure you I am quite real
(Sheldon:)and I'm having regular intercourse
with your daughter.